insurance-forums.net 2019-07-04

# Privacy Policy News & Agent Discussion

  * Insurance Forums recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.
  * This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the Insurance Forums web site.
  * By registering to Insurance Forums you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address. No extremely personal information, such as Social Security or Credit Card numbers are required by us.
  * Insurance Forums stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from ‘trusted’ internet sites, such as Insurance Forums. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](https://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)
  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.
  * Google’s use of the [DART cookie](https://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.
  * Google Analytics uses data from Google’s Interest-based advertising or 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests).
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](https://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).
  * Insurance Forums sends out various emails to our registered members, including but not limited to transactional email for new posts, site updates, newsletters, offers and site changes. To opt out of receiving email from us, please send an email address to admin@insurance-forums.com with the word remove, or [click here](https://insurance-forums.com/community/unsubscribe/) to remove yourself automatically”
  * Insurance Forums will not sell any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant United States legislation. Insurance Forums reserves the right to divulge personal information to third parties if you have violated any of the forum rules. Any user who joins the forum with multiple user accounts waives all rights to have their personal information remain private. Violation of this and all other rules as decided solely by the website management will result in the user waiving any rights to the covenants of this privacy policy.
  * All other information provided by you goes into a “public profile” and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Control Panel in the forums.
  * You have the right for the personal information held at Insurance Forums to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Control Panel in the forums. If you are having issues with this, please contact us if you need help.
  * Insurance Forums will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.
  * This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to [COPPA](https://www.ftc.gov/coppa/index.html), our site does NOT cater to children. “Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children” require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. Since we do not cater to this age group, no COPPA exists on Insurance Forums
  * This Privacy Policy and the forum rules posted at [rules page](https://insurance-forums.com/community/help/forum-rules/) may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page and the [rules page](https://insurance-forums.com/community/help/forum-rules/) for updates and changes. If you have any questions regarding your privacy, then [Contact Us](https://insurance-forums.com/contact-us/)
